### AMANDA FICI WESTIN

amanda.fici@gmail.com github.com/a-westin linkedin.com/in/amanda-fici-westin-7619ab1b1 a-westin.github.io/afw-portfolio

### **Summary**

Web Developer with a passion for clean, attractive design, leveraging my leadership skills and keen eye for detail, honed over several years in the hospitality industry; excellent communication skills, both written and verbal; creative problem-solver able to multitask well and learn new tasks quickly

#### **Technical Skills**

Earned a certificate in full stack web development: proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and related libraries; familiar with server-side and RESTful APIs, ORM, and the MERN stack

## **Projects**

**Verdant** – Repository: github.com/a-westin/verdant
Deployed Application: verdant-thumbs.herokuapp.com

• Full-stack MERN app that features Bootstrap styling to provide a streamlined, intuitive UX. Verdant provides houseplant hobbyists with a forum for researching relevant topics, saving favorite articles/plants, and chatting with other users

**Bookish** – Repository: github.com/a-westin/bookish Deployed Application: gt-bookish.herokuapp.com

• A virtual book club app that utilizes MySQL and Handlebars. Users can search for books by author and will be shown any existing clubs currently in progress; alternatively, users may create their own club

**Dinner Decider** – Repository: github.com/a-westin/dinner-decider

Deployed Application: aimeecesler.github.io/dinner-decider

• Browser-based app created with JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, and CSS. Utilizes user location in order to suggest a nearby restaurant at random, employing Zomato and Mapbox APIs

# **Experience**

Feb-July 2020

### **Moveable Feast**

Atlanta, GA

Director of Hospitality

 Main point of contact for clients at events; anticipated clients' needs to ensure best possible experience; managed staff for larger events; assisted with food setup/styling

#### Jan 2017-Jan 2020 Kimball House

Decatur, GA

Assistant General Manager/Events Coordinator

- Oversaw front of house operations prior to and during service; interacted with guests at each point in their experience in order to ensure that standards of service were upheld; worked closely with chef team to facilitate interactions between front of house and back of house staff, as well as to provide guests with an optimal dining experience
- Direct supervisor for maître d' staff; trained all employees and provided feedback or discipline as necessary
- Coordinated private events of all natures, leading guests through the process from start to finish. Personally managed events whenever possible; followed-up with hosts afterward to ensure satisfaction

## July 2013-Oct 2016 Van Michael Salon

Atlanta, GA

Closing Manager

- Key-holder: opened and closed salon with access to cash and safe. Responsible for daily financial paperwork
- Oversaw Guest Services staff on day-to-day basis, reported to Salon Manager. Interacted with guests throughout their entire experience (during check-in and check-out, booking of future appointments, assisting with questions regarding services, products, etc.)
- Maintained guest satisfaction/handled guest challenges, assisted service providers as needed
- Received orders, tracked product inventory on a daily/weekly/quarterly basis

#### **Education**

Certificate: Nov 2020 Georgia Tech Atlanta, GA

Attended 2008-12 Kennesaw State University Kennesaw, GA